recently I've been trolled by this one
person who was on me day and night I got
tweets like this I used to believe in
freedom of speech then I watch Hannibal
birds do standup
comedy here's another one Hannibal bird
should kill himself because he has no
Talent except for being a
squinty and this one really hurt you're
like a less funny Tavis
Smiley I hate being compared to Tavis
Smiley I I think I'm way funnier than Ty
Smiley that was the breaking point for
me I couldn't take it anymore so I got
the comedy sental it Department to track
down the IP address of this person from
that I was able to find out where they
live and it was on here's the
tape I love to talk a lot of trash
online but they never want to say
anything to your face
that yeses that car look like it went
through the street fighter bonus round
yikes oh look at this house I can see
why this person so angry
me
hey Amy schuma why would you do this you
trolling me no Noe then who said
Hannibal is such a strong name for a
weak act no I didn't you was just m
alonger heyan why would you do I thought
we were friends no one's friends in
comedy Hannibal wake up we're too self-
involved we can't have friends there Amy
there's no flies no there's flies here
you just you can't see them but you can
hear them I think you need to see a
therapist I don't need to go to therapy
I'm fine look I 160 lbs and I can catch
a dick whenever I want why do you keep
saying that you keep saying that true
why do you even have time to do this
don't you have a movie coming out next
week or something yes I have a movie
coming out it's going to be released
July 17th to a theater near you but that
doesn't
matter that's not what this is about
this is about you trying to move in on
my territory I'm not trying move in on
your territory Comedy Central is my
network no yes it's owned by Viacom we
can't both have TV shows yes we can I
want people to watch my show not your
show that's other the shows on Comedy
Central so what nobody watches two
television shows lots of people watch
two television shows name one person
that watches two television shows
Hannibal burs what two television shows
you watch extreme coupon and extreme
coupon and Dallas Edition there's a
Dallas Edition there a Dallas edition of
stream C it's better it's just more
specific and localized I like that part
of it good there's no fers ay pull it
together there's money for everybody out
here I got I want to buy I'm sorry it's
okay I think a lot of what you're saying
is proba true and I feel really bad
about it so what it sounds like you
never really angry at me you're mad at
yourself and you have some demons not
big demons but maybe small demons I've
got big demons you got big demons I'm
not wearing a bra but I mean they're
they're big okay so you just have some
stuff going on inside of you that you're
deal with it it's not really personal
about me so I accept your
apology um all right so we we're
good congratulations on the movie uh you
still want to grab lunch on Wednesday
yeah for sure cool could you pick me up
my car
[Applause]
exploded